Well, hello everyone!
I'm Miyuri Oguchi and I'm in charge of Equal Love's Imamoto.
So, what a surprise this time,
We are here at the Joy Museum in person.
Yay!
It's amazing, isn't it?
Look at this. Joy and Mimi-chan have already signed their autographs,
I came to AKBV&BOOKS because they are holding this event, right?
I'm so glad I could finally come.
I am so happy.
I haven't been able to see all of it yet, but it looks really gorgeous,
I would like to explore it with you.
So let's start by signing our autographs.
Okay, let's start by writing our signatures.
It's done!
Yay!
So we'll start with a random card here.
I wonder...
I was told that I could get one.
I'm a little
I'm a little nervous.
Random number one?
Yes, sir.
30 for 4.
That's right.
Wow!
Thank you very much.
I'm an equal.
Choo-choo!
Okay.
Ah!Ah!
Sana!
Mai-chan!
Ready?
Dane!
I'd like to get your autograph for my treasure.
Please write it down, Sana!
I also want to decorate my house with Mai-chan's autograph.
I hope you all get one too!
Oh!
Mistry!
What do you think?
Wow!
What?
It's from the audition announcement.
Uh, summer.
It was July 30th.
Hey.
I remember the dates here, of course.
But there's a lot of graffiti around here, too.
Oh, and here?
I'm allowed to do that.
Oh, wow!
It's us.
It's really us.
It's moving.
It's working.
They're wearing safes.
It's been a long time.
There's some kind of airing schedule over here.
Equal Love starts July 15th.
Oh, wow.Ehh.
Maimi will start on July 25th.
And
Cho-chan will start on August 6.
Oh!
Please come to all the groups!
Please come!
Here...
It says, "Thank you.
Oh, that's a great word, people.
I don't know what "I'm sorry" means.
It's my birthday.
I wonder if anyone can understand this.
I don't know.
I found something important.
What?
That's so sweet.
You're writing this?
December 9th.
To the leader of Emotan.
A seal of approval.
Yay, Jagarin!
Why? Why did you decide to write it?
I'm really bad at this.
That's good.
I feel like my handwriting is getting worse.
I'm sorry.
It was difficult.
It's not that hard.
Anda.
Yes, Anda.
Okay, okay.OK.
Good.
OK.
I miss it.
I can't speak for others
I want to write
I've got a few things written.
That's fun.
I'm writing this one too.
Garfre's words.
What was it? The song with Thanotson.
I heard the chimes.
Where's the song with the three of you?
My memory's not what it used to be.
What was what?
You'll never know.
No one does.
What?
And...
Costume.
We have costumes for you, too, Mr. Yu.
That's mine.
It's been a long time.
I can't wait to see what I'll be wearing.
I'm looking forward to it.
And you know what?
I've got some good news.
What is it?
On July 29th and 30th
We're holding Iconoiger 2023 on July 29th and 30th.
We'll be wearing
I'd like to show you the costumes I woreThe costumes I wore.
After the festival, what a surprise!
after the festival
After the festival, they will be displayed here.
That's amazing.
We haven't even seen the new costumes yet.
We haven't seen the new costumes yet.
I'm so excited.
but please come and see them up close
So please come and see it up close.
It's kind of embarrassing, though.
Did you put it on or is it in your footsteps?
I'm sure it's all washed up.
I'm sure it will.
Try it on.
And next...
I've come to the back of the panel.
There are some cute girls here.
I'd like to talk to them.
What are you doing?
What are you writing?
Hey, sweetie.
I don't know what to do.
Our first single...
"You'll Fall in Love This Summer
After that, you're going to tie the knot...
I knew I was in love.
Yes, I did.
It says Hii-chan fell in love.
It says Hiiichan fell in love.
Nice.Like
I did.
It's cute.
It's written by Mr. Sasayaru.
Oh, my.
He's drawing something like that.
The look of a man who's found a friend.
What's he writing?
I always do this every year.
I make Hanane chocolates and stuff like that.
It's called chocolate melancholy.
Self-portrait
Self-portrait.
It's so nice!
Thank you very much.
May I?
Can I have it here?
That would be great.
Thank you very much.
It's very big.
It's huge.
Maybe it looks like him.
What do you think?
Does it look like him?
That's Ana-san.
Nacchan did it for me.
She's so good!
Thank you!
Okay, next.
Let's go this way.I'll go this way.
Oh!
What's this?
It's a picture.
I'm looking forward to receiving your messages here.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please write your thoughts and feelings
and put them here.
Not from us.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please write a lot!
Oh my God, there's so many schools over here.
That's it!
Triple zeitgeist.
He's so cute!
I feel like I'm being stared at.
I like standing here.
I'd love to be a teacher.
But you know... there's a school like this.
I wonder what it would be like.
34 students? That's like...
That's like one class.
That's true.
So cute!
Maybe too cute.
Happy school.
I made a mistake.
I heard it's life-size.
But...
I'd like to say one thing.
Put the white parts together.
I was life-size.I was life-size.
I was life-size without the white parts.
Hey, this guy...
He's huge.
I'm sure.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's tiny.
Come with me.
Maybe this is it.
What do you think?
Including white.
14 points.
Including white, it's an investment.
It depends on the members.
There's a bit of a margin of error.
Lilia can't be the same height as Lisa.
Can I ask you not to take Lilia?
It's a ton of money.
That's what it looks like.
It's a highlight.
We're done here for now.
But this is where the ticket holders can enter.
On the other side...
Anyone can come here at a moment's notice and enter.
Anyone can come in at a moment's notice.
Oh!
With a delay.
You can say that.
That's right.
Why not?
Actually.As a matter of fact.
Today in the living room...
It was that little girl, Hannah.
You've come in a hurry, haven't you?
Thank you.
Welcome home.
Let's go together from here.
Without Hana...
I love you.
I took your picture.
I'm not good at it, so I asked you.
I've been waiting for you.
Sorry I'm late.
It's not Hannah's fault.
I've never been this late before.
It's all right.
You were late?
That's enough talk.
Let's go.
It wasn't just the softness, was it?
All of it.
All of it?
Okay, let's talk about lines.
Norsen, norsen, norsen... a whole series of them.
Let's just not go on.
Go on.
I was just saying...
It's a space where anyone can come in.
It's a space where you can buy goods.
I thought this was cute.
So cute!
I want to put 34 of them in a row.I want to put 34 of them together.
This is so cute!
I want to put them in front of the TV.
I'm sure you're right.
I'd love to put them in front of the TV.
And these acrylic stands.
It's so cute.
I wonder if anyone else has noticed this... ours.
That's right.
Don't our poses remind you of something?
Chinking rin
This is actually a picture of us in our early days.
We're all taking pictures of our early poses.
I tried to match them up a little bit.
Yeah.
It was a little bit of sensitivity.
A little bit.
It was like, "Dong!
It was more than fresh, wasn't it?
You did it.
This is our member's playful side.
This is called a key chain.
How do you think we're going to use it?
I don't know how to use it.
I can write on it like this.
That's nice too.
It's also cute to put on a plus sign.
There's a machine over there that makes stickers.
I'm so happy.
You can make name stickers.
Here's a key ring to put it on.
You can add your favorite member's acrylic keychain to it.Add your favorite member's acrylic keychain here.
If you add acrylic key chains of your favorite members and make them your guess, it will be like a "guess who" café.
It's like a "guess who" cafe!
I think it can be used in many ways!
So cute!
Your name and your sister's name
I'll collaborate with them!
It's like "ayaga-san"!
Yes, you can put it in two lines
I can write two lines.
Imi is doing it right now.
I'm lost!
What do you mean, lost?
I thought I'd have Mirinyan tell you.
It's like she's making a Hii-chan with Mirinya's face.
He thought of a line he'd like Mirinya to say.
Is she going to have a line too?
He's really doing a good job.
That's great!
Why don't you just say "Good luck, Hii-chan" or something?
Let's make it!
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure
I hope it's okay.
He's here.
He's early.
Wow, nice.
You're supposed to put it on this.
It's a good luck charm every time.
It's so good!
I'm sorry I made it without your permission, Miri.
I'm so happy.Glad to hear it.
That kind of thing is too dorky.
That's so funny.
This is so cool!
It's a little bit douchy.
That's a little bit too dorky.
That's too dskoy
Doscoi.
Ew, super cute!
I think you may have hit the nail on the head with the musical notes.
Oh, I love it!
What are you going to put it on?
I'm not going to put it on this.
If I put it on, I might lose it.
I'll go get it as is.
So...
Hey.
Shall we trade?
Let's trade.
A big one.
I wrote it down.
That's a great card sticker.
Yay!
Trade!
The trade worked.
Oh, that's so cute!
I'm so glad you did it.
What did you do with it?
Very well done, Seal.
It's good.
It's cute.
Very well done to the boy who got a 100 on his test.This is very well done to the child who answered 100 points on the test.
Very well done seal
Teacher
Star, flower circle star
Star, flower circle, sticker
Okay, everyone!
How was the Japanese anomaly jam?
Did you enjoy it?
This time, we are going to have the event in Tokyo from July 15
And Osaka from July 22nd.
I hope many of you will come!
And you know what?
For those of you who can't make it there
You can also watch it online!
Nice!
What does that mean?
After this event is over, you will be able to watch it online.
Please look forward to the information after this event!
We have a test coming up, and I'm sure we'll have a lot of fun and love to share with you.
I hope we can all have a lot of fun and deliver a lot of love to everyone.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
Thank you very much.
See you all again!
Bye bye!
Se-no!
Hey!
Shoka!
Alice!
Alice is out!
I got Alice!
Here it is!
With Momoka!With Momoka!
Momo-taka? Another one!
He's so cute! Stroked!
I'm so happy!
Alice!
Let's get your autograph!
Seino!
Hana-san!
My sister loves Hana-san so much.
I won't even raise my hand.
She's so creepy.
What's this!
Who's that?
I'll have to put it on the butterfly.
What happened to "bird"?
I don't know.
I just love it.
You can still do it.
You can do it.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
No one had anything.
Write "should be able to do it.
Sequential numbering. You can do it.
You're so cute.
Chiara's in?
That's great.
If anyone wants to make stickers...
Wait, I'm in trouble.
I'm gonna make you a Chiara.
What? She's so cute.
Chiara!
I love Chiara.I love Chiara's.
Kiara's is cute too!
Kiara-san!
Isn't she the best?
I'd like to get stickers of all the members.
If you're in school or something...
You can put them on your notebooks and stuff.
Even if you don't
Even if you don't want to go into the museum
Please stop by!
If you like me
If you're a fan of mine, please make one just like mine.
I hope you will all try it!
Miyagi Ramen Boy
In commemoration of the formation of
Here is V1!
Where is V2?
V1.
Let's continue to eat ramen together!
We're ramen buddies.